CURRICULUM VITAE

Kwasi Appiah Takyi



Ustanova Studentski Centar, Tosin Bunar, Beograd Mobile: (+381)616378732 Email:kwasiappiahtakyi@gmail.com

Profile & Goal

As a Master Applied Mathematician, I am responsible for collecting data, analysing it, and presenting my findings to solve practical problems in business, engineering, finance, and science. Skills: conducting research and applying mathematical knowledge to practical problems.

Skills Summary:

- Organizational skills.
- Excellent quantitative and qualitative analytic skills.
- Confident in leading projects, keeping records and organizing meetings.
- Excellent interpersonal, organizational and communication skills.
- Presenting findings to diverse audience.
- Data analysis.

I.T Skills

- Microsoft office word, excel and power point.
- Latex.
- Matlab (intermediate).
- Python (intermediate).
- Lindo (basic).

Education

Date	Programme	Institution
2022 – 2024	MSc. Applied Mathematics	University of Belgrade (MATF), Serbia.
	(Numerical Mathematics & Optimiz	ation)
May-Aug 2022	Serbian Language (Certificate A1)	Faculty of Philology, UoB, Serbia.
2013 - 2017	BSc. Mathematics	University of Energy and Natural Resources.
2008 - 2012	General Science	Ghana Secondary Technical School, Takoradi.

Academic awards

2022 - 2024	World in Serbia & Ghana Scholarship Secretariat, Serbia
2013 - 2017	Fiaseman rural bank Scholarship, Western-Region, Ghana
2008 - 2012	Gold fields Limited (AGL) scholarship, Tarkwa – Damang.

Work Experience

Date	Position and Responsibilities	Company/Institution
March,2024 – date	Electoral Committee (I.T Personnel)	WSSSR (Serbia)
13 th – 27 th March.2023	Student Internship	UoB, CLab (Belgrade, Serbia)

- Computer hardware.
- Computer software.
- Classification of hardware.
- Installation of software.

Feb – May.2022	Pupils Teacher	Green Energy Academy, Bui-Ghana
2018 – 2022	Teaching Assistant	NABCO (Chiraa Islamic School)

- Organizing tutorials for students.
- Guiding class discussions.
- Returning assignments to students in accordance with a decided deadline.
- Organizing quizzes and invigilation.
- Assisting students in understanding a topic.
- Assisting my supervisor supervise final year students project work.

Teaching Assistant

• Marking and grading students' examinations and assignments.

June – Aug. 2016

2017-2018

Business Intelligence Intern

Fiaseman Rural Bank (HV Branch)

NSS (UENR)

- Assisting customers in checking their account balance and cashing checks (customer service).
- Opening account manually and electronically for new customers.
- Reconciliation of account.
- Receiving students' fees and recorded of overdraft.
- Attending workshops.
- Marketing Products.

June – Aug. 2015

Business Intelligence Intern

ABSA (BK) (Project Dept.)

Assisting project managers and manageresses in organizing and verifying data and business documents.

- Attending meetings with supervisors.
- Verifying compositional data to ensure correct data for accounting activities.
- Organizing NPA training for ABSA working staffs.
- Making significant mathematical calculations on product for projects.

Workshop & Training

4 th Sept.2020	Entrepreneurship, College for Community and Organizational Development. Sunyani-Odumase. Ghana.
11 th Aug.2020	Star Life Assurance. Sunyani, Ghana.
23 rd May.2019	Job fair, Ghanaian-German Centre for jobs. Ghana International Trade Fair Centre, Accra. Ghana.